Finding aid for the Jerry Lewis papers LSC.2124
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Public Relations, 1956-2012
  - Subseries 1.1: Press Clippings, 1969-2012
    - Press Clippings, 2006 March (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 April (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 2006 May (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 2006 May (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 2006 June (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 2006 June (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 2006 July (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 2006 July (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 August (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 September (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 October (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 November (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 December (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 January (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 February (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 March (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 April (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 May (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 June (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 July (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 August (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 September (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 October (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 November (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 December (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 January (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 February (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 March (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 April (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 May (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 July (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 August (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 September (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 October (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 November (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 December (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 January (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 February (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 March (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 April (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 May (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 June (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 July (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 August (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 September (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 October (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 November (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Press Clippings, 2009 December (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 January (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 February (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 March (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 April (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 May (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 June (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 July (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 August (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 September (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 October (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 November (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 December (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 January (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 February (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 March (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 April (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 May (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 June (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 July (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 August (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 September (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 October (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 November (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 2011 December (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 2012 January (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 2012 February (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 2012 March (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 2012 April-September (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 2012 July (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files: Brown, George, 1999 July-2001 June (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files: California State University, Army Distance Education, 2000 August-2008 January (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files: Crooks, Hulda, 1986 May-August (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files: Dolittle Lobbying Investigation, 2006 January-April (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files: Elections, 2000 May-2008 February (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files: Elections, 40th District, 1998 June-2000 August (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Subject Files: Elections, 41st District, 2002 January-February (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Subject Files: Elections, 42nd District, 1999 March-2001June (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Subject Files: Elections, San Bernardino County, 2000 March-2002 February (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Subject Files: Highland Community Projects, 1999 November-2001 January (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Subject Files: House Republican Research Committee, First Day Press, 1985 January 15 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files: Important Articles, 1979 January-1987 August (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Subject Files: Important Articles, 1979 April-1984 March (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Subject Files: Important Articles, 1981 September (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Subject Files: Important Articles, 1981 September-1983 November (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Subject Files: Inland Action Group, 2000 February (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Subject Files: Interstate 15 and Interstate 40 Exchange, 1994 May-2003 May (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Background Information, 1981 September-November (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Bimonthly and Weekly, 1976 January-December (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Bimonthly, 1977 January-December (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Bimonthly, 1978 January-August (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, For the Senior View, 1978 January-November (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1980 July (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 February (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 March (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 April (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 May (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 June (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 July (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 September (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 October (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 November (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1981 December (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 January (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 February (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 March (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 April (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 May (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 June (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 July (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 August (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 September (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1982 December (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 January (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 February (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 March (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 April (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 May (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 June (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 July (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 August (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 September (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 October (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1983 November (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1984 April (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1984 May (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1984 August (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1984 September (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1984 October (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1985 February (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1986 January-April (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Subject Files: Jerry Lewis's Column, Weekly, 1986 September (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Subject Files: McKay, David O., circa 1970 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Subject Files: Reapportionment, Redistricting, 1999 June-2002 February (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Subject Files: Republican Organizations' Newsletters, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Subject Files: Retirement, 2012 January (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Subject Files: San Bernardino International Airport, 1999 July-2002 February (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Subject Files: San Bernardino Lakes Plan, 1999 December-2002 February (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Subject Files: Vietnam War, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files: Viewpoint Article, 1983 November (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 1.2: Press Releases, 1979-2005
    This subseries contains press releases generated by Jerry Lewis's office during almost the full span of his congressional tenure, from 1979 to 2005. Most heavily concentrated during the 1980s, Lewis's press releases cover his positions on the United States' relations with Poland and El Salvador in 1981, his election as chairman of the Republican Research Committee in 1985, his introduction of the American gold coin in 1985, his views on defense spending in 1986, and much more. Of special interest to researchers may be the drafts, edits, and occasional background research accompanying the finished press releases, all of which provide an inside view of the crafting of Lewis's official messages to the public.
    This subseries is organized chronologically by year.
    - Press Releases, 1979 August-1980 June (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - The Republican Freshman Class, 1980 February 27 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Lewis Pushes for Bill to Protect Social Security Benefits, 1981 January 6 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Lewis Calls Carter Budget "Shell Game", 1981 January 15 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Hostage Release Signals New Beginning, 1981 January 20 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Lewis Testifies in Support of Small Business Administration Nominee, 1981 February (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Lewis Cites Increase in Antisemitism as Cause for Concern, 1981 February 16 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Lewis Introduces Bill to Impose Quality Standards on Imported Grapes, 1981 February 16 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Press Releases, 1981 March (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Lewis Introduces Legislation to Encourage Technological Innovations, 1981 April 7 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Lewis Urges Environmental Protection Agency to Allow Use of Bayleton in Coachella Valley, 1981 April 23 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Lewis Testifies in Support of Palo Verde Diversion Dam, 1981 April 28 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Lewis Introduces Legislation to Eliminate Peanut Shortage, 1981 April 29 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - House Passes President's Bipartisan Budget, 1981 May 7 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - National Small Business Week, 1981 May 14 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - House Passes President's Tax Package, 1981 June 27 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - House Subcommittee to Hold Hearings on Highway 86, 1981 June 30 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - House Approves Funding for Medfly, 1981 July 27 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Lewis Coordinates Meeting to Discuss Medfly Spread, 1981 September 11 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Lewis Works Towards Emergency Funds for the Medfly, 1981 September 14 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Lewis Testifies on Small Business Bill, 1981 September 15 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Lewis Serves as United States Advisor to U.S.A. Delegation to World Bank, 1981 September 29 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Lewis Joins to Disapprove AWACS Planes Sale, 1981 October 14 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Lewis Introduces Clean Air Act Resolution, 1981 October 21 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Lewis Supports Resolution to Restrain Government Spending, 1981 October 30 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Vietnam Veterans Memorial Called "Black Ditch", 1982 January 12 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Do Not Lower Date Import Standards, 1982 January 28 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - American Taxpayer Subsidizing Polish Repression, 1982 February 5 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Lewis to Meet Army Secretary on San Jacinto- Bautista Creek, 1982 March 2 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Lewis Joins Congressional Housing Caucus, 1982 March 4 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Appropriations Committee Rejects Student Loan Cut, 1982 March 26 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Lewis Announces Congressional Art Competition, 1982 April 1 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Lewis Praises Reagan Proposal for Deep Nuclear Cuts, 1982 May 9 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Death Valley Health Clinic to Continue Operation, 1982 May 14 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Lewis Selected for El Salvador- Guatemala Trip, 1982 June 23 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Lewis Responds to Haig Resignation while in El Salvador, 1982 June 25 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - President Signs Bill Calling for Declaration of Default on Polish Debts, 1982 July 19 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Peace Corps Meeting Rescheduled for October 19, 1982 September 27 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Lewis Sends a "Special Flag" to San Bernardino High School, 1982 November 10 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Lewis Urges Support for MX Missile, 1982 December 7 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Task Force Recommends Agenda for Regulatory Reform, 1983 January 17 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Lewis Appointed to Housing and Urban Development Subcommittee, 1983 February 2 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Lewis Introduces Bill to Repeal New Tip Rule, 1983 February 25 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Task Force Supports Natural Gas Reforms, 1983 March 3 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Lewis Says, "Link American Aid and Credit to Nuclear Arms Reduction, 1983 March 9 (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Lewis Introduces Bill to Repeal 10% Withholding Tax, 1983 March 15 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Lewis to Hold Community Forums in West End, 1983 March 22 (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - Lewis to Appear on "It's Your Business" Syndicated Television Program, 1983 March 23 (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - Lewis Appointed to Air Force Academy Board of Visitors, 1983 April 8 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Victor Valley Waitresses Forces Tip Tax Repeal, 1983 April 11 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Lewis to Hold Forum in Barstow, 1983 April 12 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - Lewis to Hold Forum in Needles, 1983 April 12 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Lewis to Hold Forum in Victorville, 1983 April 19 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Lewis to review Charges of Abuse by Interior Department, 1983 April 25 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - Lewis Announces Congressional Art Competition, 1983 April 26 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - House Republican Task Force Says, "Sunset the Interstate Commerce Commission", 1983 May 13 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - General Accounting Office Finds Inequitable Wages at Government Printing Office, 1983 June 14 (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - Lewis to Hold Forums in Redlands and Yucaipa, 1983 June 21 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - Lewis Appointed to Foreign Assistance Commission, 1983 June 27 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - House Task Force Examines Postal Services, 1983 July 27 (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - Press Releases, 1983 August (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - Lewis Calls Soviet Action "Barbaric and Ruthless", 1983 September 1 (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - Republican Task Force Asks, "Are the Cafe Standards Out- to- Lunch?", 1983 September 16 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - GOP Task Force Report Offers Congress Alternatives to Legislative Veto, 1983 October 6 (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - Congressman Bob Michel Press Release: Lewis Elected to House Leadership Position, 1983 November 2 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - Lewis Introduces Bill to Compensate Flood Victims, 1983 November 18 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - Lewis Schedules Press Conferences with Department of Education Official, 1983 November 30 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - National Industry Policy: New Rhetoric, Old Ideas, 1984 February 6 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Lewis to Seek Reelection for a Fourth Term, 1984 February 17 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - Lewis Calls for Hearings on Colorado Disaster Assistance Bill, 1984 February 21 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - Lewis to Serve on Reagan- Bush Steering Committee, 1984 February 29 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - Lewis Announces Congressional Art Competition, 1984 March 30 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - Lewis Named to United States Delegation of Observers in El Salvador, 1984 May 4 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - Winner of 1984 Congressional Art Competition, 1984 May 30 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - Lewis Legislation Effort to Apply Brakes on Federal Spending, 1984 June 18 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - Lewis Reelected to House Leadership Position, 1984 December 3 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - Bipartisan Coalition Introduces Gold Coin Bill, 1985 February 27 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - Lewis Announces Congressional Art Competition, 1985 March 25 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - Lewis's Report Cites Concern on Expiring Congressional Legislation, 1985 May 16 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Winner of 1985 Congressional Art Competition, 1985 May 17 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - Foreign Military Assistance Cut, 1985 July 17 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - California's Outer Continental Shelf Protection and Development, 1985 July 25 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - Lewis Claims Major NASA Victory, 1985 July 30 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - Budget Compromise is First Step, 1985 August 1 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - Wave of Democracy Spreading, Lewis Says, 1985 September 24 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Lewis Joins Effort to Combat Osteoporosis, 1985 October 7 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Lewis Sponsors Comprehensive Trade Bill, 1985 October 10 (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - Lewis Named to House- Senate Conference, 1985 November 7 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Gold Coin Will Hit United States by Storm, Lewis Says, 1985 November 12 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - Gold Coin Bill Clears Senate Hurdle, 1985 November 18 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - Department of Justice Indictment of General Dynamics Corporation, 1985 December 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - President Signs Gold Coin Legislation, 1985 December 17 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - Press Releases, 1986 January-February (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Congressman Lewis Announces Art Competition, 1986 March 27 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - Lewis Announces Comprehensive Acid Rain Legislation, 1986 April 11 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - Lewis Announces President's Commission Hearing on Americans Outdoors, 1986 April 14 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - Lewis Questions Egyptian Criticism, Continued Assistance, 1986 April 17 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Lewis Seeks Funding for Ontario Airport Vehicle Access Program, 1986 April 23 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Lewis Announces Seminar, "Congress: Past, Present, Future", 1986 May 12 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - Lewis Announces Approval of Passport Service in Apple Valley, 1986 May 23 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Lewis Commends Rogers' Commission Report, 1986 June 10 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Lewis Announces House Passage of Anti- Drug Legislation, 1986 September 11 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - America's Money as Good as Gold Again, 1986 September 9 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Tough Drug Measure will Put Pushers Where They Belong, 1986 September 11 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Tough Anti- Drug legislation will Send Clear Signal, 1986 October 8 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Press Releases, 1988 September-December (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Press Releases, 1990 February (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Press Releases, 1994 May-December (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Press Releases, 1995 January-December (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial Fundraising and Public Awareness Kit, 1995 March 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases 1996 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases, 1996 February-November (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1997 January-November (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases 1997-1999 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases, 1998 January-November (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1999 February-November (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Lewis Secures 7.5 Million Dollars for Inland Empire, 1999 June 23 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases, 2000 February-December (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases, 2001 February-December (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 2002 February-October (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 2003 February-November (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases, 2004 April-November (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases, 2005 July-November (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 1.3: District Mailers, 1971-2007
    This subseries consists of the district mailers Lewis's office sent to his constituents between 1968 and 2007. While it includes some mailers sent during his time as a California State Assemblyman, these files are most concentrated on his years in the U.S. House of Representatives, particularly in the 1980s. Due to redistricting during his tenure, Lewis represented the 35th, 37th, 40th, and 41st districts in Congress, shifts that are reflected in the file names. The district mailers take the form of newsletters and contain topics important to his voters, including tax increases, immigration reform, inflation, government assistance for seniors and veterans, and disaster relief. Of special note are surveys conducted through the mailers, which provide insight into the political opinions of his constituency, especially in the area of federal spending. Researchers may also be interested in the rubber printing dies included in this subseries, which were used to create the headings for Lewis's earliest mailers as a California State Assemblyman.
    - Capitol Report, California State Assembly: Prints and Printing Dies, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - California State Assembly, 1971-1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1979 May (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1979 October (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1979 December (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1980 February (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1980 April (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1980 July (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1980 September (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1981 March (Box 13, Folder 24)